You got the answer,
so you deserve the prize.
I don't need money.
Once I am old enough to use that money,
its monetary value would have dropped.
Is that so?
I'd like land.
A place with lots of plants and trees.
I like this area, right here.
That land was used to make pottery. It's useless.
(Gyeonggi Province, Seongnam, Bundang-dong)
Do you want the land in Bundang that badly?
Let's see.
How does 160,000m² sound?
(Gyeonggi Province, Seongnam, Bundang-dong)
This small village will become a new city,
home to 390,000 people.
According to the government's New Town development plan,
on Seongnam's Bundang area,
about 105,000 medium to large apartment blocks will be built.
They will reduce the burden on Gangnam's housing demand...
by housing 420,000 people.
What an incredible change this place went through.
There was just one reservoir...
with fields and rice paddies reaching the horizons.
People say that Bundang...
is the next best place to live, second to paradise.
Did you know then...
that this place would become like this?
Do you simply have good discernment?
Or are you just lucky?
I owe it to a grandfather who gifted me 160,000m² of land.
Not anyone gets to be born your grandson.
Does that make me lucky?
From the land here,
do you know how much you made?
Welcome, sir.
This way, please.
The 24 million dollars you asked for.
Good.
The compensation for the purchase of land was 14 million.
Ten million was from selling the nearby commercial land.
A total of 24 million dollars...
is what you earned.
Would you like to count it out?
How will you manage to spend all this?
If you buy books with it,
you'll never read them all in your lifetime.
If you spend it on tuition,
you'll have to get a hundred degrees.
If you're afraid, leave it with me.
I'll pay you more in interest than a bank does.
(Reborn Rich)
Do Jun is still a kid, isn't he?
It's only natural.
Where could he have seen such a huge amount?
Sir, Hangang Bank's Namdaemun Branch called.
Do Jun has exchanged the money in the account into dollars.
Shouldn't you ask him what it's for?
He may be clever,
but it's too much money for a 20-year-old.
Does money choose people depending on their age?
Let's find out if Do Jun...
is a fortunate boy,
or a boy with foresight.
It's just luck.
How else can you explain it?
What could a little boy know about real estate...
that he'd ask for land in Bundang?
No one can beat someone with great luck.
Doesn't that make him even scarier?
What does Father say almost every day?
You don't become rich by working hard.
It's up to the heavens.
Do Jun made 24 million dollars...
by just pointing at a map.
Father could think...
his youngest grandson is blessed.
Wait.
Is that why? Isn't it weird?
Dad gave that massive sum to a kid who just started college...
and let him manage it himself.
He's not that kind of person.
He never let us do anything like that.
Not even Seong Jun, his eldest grandson.
Right?
Seong Jun is the eldest heir,
and he was exiled in the name of study.
Why does Father play favourites with the youngest, Do Jun?
That money.
It's the price of our father's life.
If not for Do Jun,
when the plane exploded in mid air,
Father would've died in it.
Who cares if it's 24 million or 240 million?
It's too early for such a fuss.
Don't you feel ashamed?
You're jealous about a 20-year-old boy's allowance.
You're grown-up adults.
Do you really think so?
That it's allowance?
That it's a simple gift?
It could be a test.
Father could be testing the boy with plans on picking a successor.
What is it that I am
Trying to look for?
Where to is it that I am
Flowing so endlessly?
The upcoming New York Film Market.
Take me with you, Father.
To the Film Market?
I got into university,
but I have lots of time until the semester starts.
I'd like to travel,
and maybe do some advising on what films you should invest in.
You'll be an investment advisor?
You know I have a good eye.
I think I'm the one who got you this office.
I must release this movie on Christmas at all costs?
Do Jun.
You're still young and don't know about movies.
Christmas movies are for families.
Who'd want to watch a gloomy movie about a kid...
left alone at home while his family went travelling?
And you still...
want me to import this movie?
So you want to go to the New York Film Market?
Yes. Who knows?
This time, it might not be just an office.
Perhaps I could buy you a whole building.
There was no me anymore
We are still young We still have a nice future
Now wipe up your cold tears
Come back home
Let's go home now.
- You go ahead. - Come with me.
I'm not Seo Tai Ji.
Oh, gosh...
- Hey, Do Jun. - What?
Just because you got into law top of the class,
don't get fancy and have dreams...
of passing the bar while you're still in college.
What?
Play. Have fun.
Go on group blind dates, regular blind dates, casual dates,
- and go out with someone. - Hang on.
Are they all different?
Are they the same, then? They have different terms.
Don't do that.
Don't make the face of a man who already lived a lifetime.
- What? - Don't do that either.
- I'll do it. - Go away.
Wait, what's that?
- No way. - What do we do now?
What is it?
Excuse me.
- They'd caused a fuss... - Excuse me.
- Coming through. - Sorry.
- They announced their retirement. - What is it?
As of today, January 31, 1996...
Are they disbanding or retiring?
They're retiring.
- Oh, no... - Jeez.
(Seo Min Yeong)
Why are they retiring?
My loves.
They're retiring because the pain of creating music is too much.
(Seo Min Yeong)
What's this?
This is a look I've never seen on your face.
I can't believe that's her face when she was 20.
Do you know her?
Did you meet her? When?
What?
Oh...
In 20 years' time.
"In 20 years' time."
He's at it again.
Move, mister.
- Move. - Okay.
- I can't see. - I'm not a mister.
Chang Je, are you getting old?
You shouldn't be up this early. What's going on?
Why are you coming to see me?
Take a look at this, Father.
(Seoul District Public Prosecutors' Office)
(Report on Special Investigation into Hando Steel)
I don't think Hando Steel will last a month.
It's a great chance to buy it up cheap.
They took out too many loans to try to expand.
If you underwrite Hando Steel now,
wouldn't it help subsidiaries that use steel...
such as Soonyang Heavy Machinery, Motors, and Machinery?
How will they handle this much debt?
If the government vouches for us,
we can extend the repayment deadline to suit us.
Can we trust President YS?
If Hando Group were to break up now,
it would cause huge turmoil.
The President would want to prevent the worst.
Having a prosecutor son-in-law...
is so reassuring.
I thought I should give you...
one last gift while I still work there.
What?
Are you going to start a law firm?
Before the general election in April,
the President will recruit talent to join his party.
I'd love to join as a legal advisor and run for office.
The National Assembly is on an island.
It'll be very windy out there. Do you want to get into politics?
You can give me a sail.
I want to venture into bigger waters for Soonyang.
I'll see...
if my son-in-law's ship can survive the sea.
I'll do my best not to let you down, Father.
Something that dreamy would never happen.
One day, will a Korean movie ever beat Hollywood movies...
to win Best Picture at the Academy Awards?
That's something out of a sci-Fi cartoon that makes me emotional.
It won't be easy.
The Academy Awards tend to snuff non-English movies.
I'm too imaginative.
If that day comes,
a Korean song might even reach Billboard's Top 100.
I know.
What I'm saying is as likely as Team Korea...
reaching the semifinals of the FIFA World Cup.
Can't a man dream?
Don't you know dreams come true?
Darn you. Wait up, Dad.
Yes.
Dreams do come true.
- Oh. - I'm sorry.
What the... This is just not fair.
Darn it.
Are you Korean?
Shoot.
If you mean nationality, no.
If you mean where I was born, yes.
We're halfway around the world.
You're not expecting a friendly hug, are you?
Look.
Because of you, I just became the investor...
with the most rotten luck in the whole of this market.
Oh, then...
I'm truly sorry.
I'll pay you for the donut.
- How much do you want? - Ten million dollars!
Ten million dollars?
What are you talking about?
One donut costs ten million dollars?
I always eat a donut before I decide what to invest in.
I've never broken it once.
It's a principle, routine, and jinx. Anyway,
it's my most important, necessary,
and sufficient condition of investing.
This donut is from a shop in Midtown that's 30 minutes from here.
And I have just ten minutes to decide what to invest in.
Without a donut,
in this market where ten million dollars will change hands,
because of clumsy you.
You'll pay me back?
This donut cost a dollar, but it's worth ten million to me.
How much will you pay me?
Never bet on things...
that you aren't sure about.
Do you get that?
That...
Do Jun! We're over here.
Okay. I'm coming.
What a weirdo.
"Titanic."
The "Titanic" fever is going strong.
Nominated for 14 Academy Awards, the most in Academy history,
at the 70th Academy Awards...
I should invest in "Titanic?"
Yes.
Not for import or distribution rights...
but the production?
Yes.
That way, you get a part of the massive profit.
It goes here.
There are three arches.
- Shall we bet? - Yes.
Do Jun. The reason you wanted to come here...
was because you had this movie in mind from the start?
Hey. Look, Father.
My gosh.
Wow. Nice.
Are you convinced it will be a hit?
Like "Home Alone" last time?
You know I have a good hunch.
Trust me again.
A hunch?
Father. I have a scientific...
and logical reason this movie will flop.
It'll shock you.
Blockbusters involving water...
are bound to flop.
Why?
Because the project sinks.
What?
"Cut throat Island," "Waterworld,"
and serial hit-maker James Cameron's only flop "The Abyss."
They're all about water, and they all tanked.
This is a science.
Boss, you need to think this over.
You have to think this over.
You would've never made this decision...
if you didn't drop that darn donut.
Ten million dollars into "Titanic?"
Why don't you take that ten million dollars...
and just throw it into the Atlantic Ocean?
Will you still invest in "Titanic?"
Come on. You didn't even watch "Waterworld."
I couldn't.
DiCaprio?
Who on earth will do the acting?
And the woman who looks like his aunt.
Do Koreans even know who she is?
Do you know her? I don't know her.
- No Brad Pitt or Tom Cruise. - They're Korean.
A blockbuster with zero stars?
Do you really think this will work, boss?
"Titanic."
It's about a luxury cruise ship that's only for the rich...
sinking in a gruesome manner in the middle of nowhere.
It's about the rich losing out.
People have no choice but to flock to the cinemas.
Why? Because it'll never happen in reality.
Did you hear that?
She looks like DiCaprio's aunt?
She's the real reason I want to invest in this movie.
What?
In a recession like this,
the public care very little for cute, young starlets.
They prefer mature actresses with an intellectual air...
to be their heroine.
Kate Winslet has that face.
They spent an enormous amount of money to make the movie.
It won't be profitable unless it becomes an international hit.
Following Europe,
countries in East Asia are building multiplex theatres too.
The number of movie goers will increase exponentially.
And naturally, the profitability will go up as well.
You know what a low-price high-volume policy means, right?
Are you confident?
Can I guarantee that the movie will be a hit?
Then my answer is no. However,
if it's about recovering the investment...
and securing stable profitability... Yes.
- He's right. - I'm very rational now, Rachael.
I said I dropped the donut.
I never said I didn't eat it.
What?
"Based on scientific evidence..."
is what I'd say in a situation like this.
- Hey! - How's it going?
- I'm good. - Yes.
Are you going to invest in this?
- That's what I'm thinking about. - What about you?
- I'm investing... - Do you have anything in mind?
- Power Shares? - Yes, I have...
Mason Oh.
His Korean name is Oh Se Hyeon.
Power Shares.
The director and head of APAC at Power Shares.
Hi, good afternoon.
Hi, may I help you?
Yes. I'm Jin.
I'm here to see Mason Oh.
- I got twenty on Kasparov. - Fifty on Kasparov.
We're nuts for doing this.
I want to put... If you guys let me get in on...
I'm surprised to see you here. I thought...
you'd been in a business meeting somewhere.
Thanks to you,
I became the luckiest investor on Wall Street today.
Here's your delicious cheese pizza.
Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
What's that guy doing?
Is he crazy or something?
Maybe you should order something else.
Darn it. This is so good.
This is the best cheese I've ever had.
I should've bought some shares in this cheese company back then.
It's too late now.
Darn, it's so good.
Hey, you. I wanted to say something earlier.
I am working right now.
Leave me alone, will you? Don't disturb me.
Well, that's the right move, by the way.
- Oh. - Yes, that is the right move.
That was absolutely amazing.
The supercomputer Deep Blue...
versus Kasparov, the chess champion.
What a strange world we live in.
Even a computer has a name?
Hyeon Woo, what was it called?
You know, that computer. Blue... What was it?
Dad!
- Dad! - What is it, son?
- Wow. - Why? Who won?
My gosh. Unbelievable.
Who do you think will win?
The supercomputer Deep Blue?
Or Garry Kasparov, the chess champion?
Who?
Well...
Everyone says it's the game of the century...
between a human and a computer.
But that's not what you're interested in, right?
"What is the company value of IBM, the company that made Deep Blue?"
"When and how much should I buy in to maximize my profit?"
That's why you're so engrossed in the match. Am I right?
I'll tell you who will win.
In turn, spare me your time.
You can tell me who will win when the match is still going on?
Deep Blue will win.
Invest in IBM, before this round ends.
Can I have a piece?
Well, chances are... It's 50-50 anyway.
I guess you're relying on luck. Too bad.
Deep Blue hasn't overcome the limitations of AI.
Even the engineers and developers at IBM admitted it.
But you think Deep Blue will beat Kasparov, the genius player?
Deep Blue has less than a 20-percent chance to win.
That's what all experts say. Hey, young man.
Never bet on things that you aren't sure about.
I never rely on luck when it comes to my investments.
When the game ends,
you'll want to meet me.
I'm confident.
I'm 100 percent sure that Deep Blue will win.
Hey, go away.
Oh, my gosh!
- No problem! - Yes!
- I can't believe it. - Thank you, gentlemen. Sorry, man.
What? Deep Blue won?
A supercomputer beat a human for the first time in history?
That was a fluke, right?
How did you guess it?
None of the experts on Wall Street...
predicted that Deep Blue would win.
I trusted my instincts.
What?
Had Kasparov been a mere player,
Deep Blue wouldn't have stood a chance against him.
However, I bet Kasparov, the genius chess player...
who's kept the world champion title for the past 20 years,
wanted to make history.
"Fought against AI and won,"
"thus protecting the pride of mankind."
He probably wanted a title like that.
And greed...
always clouds your judgement.
Not bad.
I'd like to invest in companies in the US.
Relying on your instincts, knowing how risky that can be?
I have you.
Use numbers to help me prove that my instincts are on point.
I'm a busy man, you see.
Enjoy the rest of your trip.
With accurate data, which is essential for investing.
And with cash.
Do you know that the minimum amount we require...
is 30,000 dollars?
I have a lot of money, Mr. Oh.
Save up as much as you can before you join the military.
Enjoy your trip. Bye.
(Jeongsimjae)
As for Hando Steel, we're estimating...
that it'd cost us about 500 million dollars.
So we'll go penniless after this deal.
Do they have something we could use to make money?
Hando Steel owns a warehouse in Busan.
If we make sure the creditors can't touch it...
and build an apartment complex in that lot,
we should be able to earn back the money fairly soon.
Sir, we've encountered an unexpected variable though.
Daeyoung Group is getting ready to bid on Hando Steel too.
The Secretary's Office informed me this morning.
Then it means Daeyoung will bid on it for sure.
Our Secretary's Office obtains Intel before the NSP does.
Right, Daeyoung makes cars, heavy equipment,
and even ships.
No wonder they want to buy a steel-producing company.
To beat Daeyoung,
we'd need at least 400 million dollars. Don't you think?
It's not even a lucrative deal.
Then should we forget about Hando Steel altogether?
I will not let Daeyoung acquire Hando Steel.
And the maximum amount we'll spend on this is 300 million.
We won't spend a penny more.
Then how...
Why are you asking me?
- Vice-Chairman. - Yes, sir.
Go make sure we can acquire Hando Steel.
Pardon?
Why? Are you not confident?
Then step down. Why are you sitting here?
What will you do?
My goodness. Thanks. This looks delicious.
Do Jun, you're such a perfect grandson.
You came all the way here...
to see your grandparents after your trip to the US.
Just like your father, you're handsome,
smart, and sweet.
Right, Jeong Rae?
I'd say he got his looks from his mother.
As for his brain... I don't know.
Use your smart brain to follow in your grandpa's footsteps...
and grow the company.
Why not study management?
Why would you suddenly want to go to law school?
He takes after his father,
so I guess he has no interest in running a business whatsoever.
Right, Do Jun?
If I study law,
I can be more helpful to Grandpa and his business.
Really?
My gosh. Is that why you decided to study law, Do Jun?
Grandma, I'm still in my first year.
At the moment, I just want to play and not think about anything.
Yes! Just play.
That's what you should do when you're in your first year.
Meet some girls too, okay?
The board meeting is over.
I see. You can go upstairs now, Do Jun.
Okay, Grandma.
- Thank you. - Just play!
Goodness, that old man is awfully stubborn.
Acquire Hando Steel, but don't spend money.
What are we supposed to do, then?
Right, Young Ki?
Do Jun, you're back!
You little rascal.
Did you see lots of cool things in the US?
- Did you eat lots of good food? - Yes, Grandpa.
Thanks to you...
I had a great trip.
Good.
What was your favourite out of all the dishes you tried there?
- Pardon me? - What was your favourite dish?
Oh.
The donut.
That brat.
Does he think he's Lee Mi Ja or Cho Yong Pil...
who just returned from his concert tour in Southeast Asia?
Goodness.
I'm talking about Do Jun.
He was in New York for a few days with his dad.
And he showed up to report to Father that he's back.
Hey. He's just 20, and he's a guy.
Guys his age are rarely that attentive.
I bet he has an ulterior motive.
At age 20, he should know how to respect his elders.
He's better than his dad.
You're so understanding.
You're incredibly magnanimous.
But you see,
did you know that Do Jun...
exchanged the 24 billion won to US dollars before his trip?
The price of our father's life?
It wouldn't have been possible without Father's permission.
He's different from his dad.
Yoon Ki never had any interest in the company.
But that boy is different. Just look at his eyes.
We have to stay frosty, Young Ki.
That it's allowance? That it's a simple gift?
It could be a test.
Go make sure we can acquire Hando Steel.
Father could be testing the boy with plans on picking a successor.
Why? Are you not confident?
Then step down. Why are you sitting here?
(Jin Young Ki)
I told the Economic Research Institute...
to prepare a report to send to Hando Steel's creditors.
If we emphasize the number of jobs that will be created...
when we acquire Hando Steel and the positive synergy,
Cheongwadae will show interest too.
Risk management is crucial as the administration is nearing its end.
Please proceed accordingly, Mr. Lee.
Yes, sir.
Hang Jae.
My old man...
What does he want from me?
Acquiring Hando Steel?
Or...
is he just not happy with anything I do?
You know what he's thinking better than his own children do.
Mr. Chairman...
would like to pass Soonyang down to someone who is like him.
And it might not be his eldest son?
Young Ki, he is giving you a chance first...
because you're his eldest son.
Focus on acquiring Hando Steel.
He wants to see the fighting spirit and persistence in you.
To him, running a company...
was like a never-ending war,
where he had to kill first in order to survive.
Sir.
As you had predicted, Vice-Chairman Jin...
asked me what you were really thinking.
I told him that you were giving him a chance...
and that nothing would change...
if he did his best to acquire Hando Steel.
I assured him.
Hang Jae.
It's such a shame.
Pardon me?
Why were you born to your parents?
I wish you were my son.
Sir, didn't you know?
I think of you as my father.
I'll leave you to it.
You see, Do Jun...
His school is pretty far from where he lives.
Send him a car.
Yes, sir.
Hello, I'm Ha In Seok from the Secretary's Office.
Hello.
Mr. Chairman sent me.
He said your school was pretty far,
so it must be hard for you to commute.
I'll be your driver from now on.
Please just drop me off in front of the gate.
I'll walk from there.
No, I'll drop you off in front of the lecture hall.
Most people at school already know who I am.
I don't want to show up with a driver and attract attention.
It won't do Grandpa any good.
Right, I'll remember that.
(Seoul National University)
I got it. I don't want to turn into a spoiled brat.
Oh, right.
You're done for the day.
You're free to decide how to spend the rest of your day.
Bye.
- Hello! - Come and take one!
- Take a look at this. - Please join us!
- Come find us! - Join us!
- Hello, take one! - Welcome!
- Hello, welcome! - Are you a freshman?
- Would you be interested? - Hi.
Come find us!
You should join us.
Jin Do Jun, at the School of Law. Right?
I study law too. I'm Kim Tae Young.
He's Gang Nam from the Department of Journalism.
Come on, why is the introduction so bland? It's between us.
Tae Young's family owns Mirae Industry.
My family owns Bando Firm.
Ji Min's grandfather has been the Prime Minister since...
So?
Seong Jun must not have told you about our club, Prestigious Club.
I did hear about it. Prestigious Club.
You used to call me casually, but now you treat me as your senior.
It was the center of Vice-Chairman Jin Seong Jun's connection.
A secretive social gathering...
of the children of prestigious families.
You don't have to act so stiff. It's nothing much.
We're just inviting you to have a meal with those of your class.
People are so strange.
They feel a sense of incongruity because of people like us.
So what? Is that our fault?
It's their inferior complex.
Yes.
What do you think, newbie?
Enough with all the talking.
Your number.
Why? Do I need your grandfather's permission to get your number?
I'll text you the location and time of your welcoming dinner.
You know it's a must to bring a partner, right?
I must stick to the rule, right?
Nice!
(Music Listening Room)
We've met before, right?
You look familiar. I definitely met you before.
Where did we meet?
You definitely have a classical taste.
You could just invite me for a meal.
Isn't this tactic way too classic?
Hello, I'm not hitting on you.
Invite you for a meal?
- When did I... - Here it is.
This is what you're looking for, right?
Let's have a meal.
("'Hello, I'm Jin Do Jun,' An Interview With Jin Do Jun...")
("Who Entered Department of Law At the Top of His Class")
There was a reason.
Are you so confident and rude...
because of your grandfather?
No way.
What's so hard about having a meal...
with a peer in my department?
Do I have to use my grandfather's power to eat with you?
If you treat me to a nice meal,
I was going to tell you...
when Seo Tai Ji was making a comeback.
I thought you might be curious.
Is it fun to tease people?
It's true, right?
You said Soonyang's better than the CIA in getting information.
That's how you heard it, right?
I knew it. Is he really making a comeback?
When?
You're going to eat with me, right?
She's there. Please stop here.
Okay.
Do you normally always wear like this?
You're a bit different from the Seo Min Yeong I know.
This? You're wrong.
You must be thinking...
that I dolled up to meet you, but...
You look better now. They're nice clothes.
Tell me now. Is it true?
Is he really making a comeback?
Seo Tai Ji, I mean.
When is he coming back?
You...
Do you really know?
After 4 years. The summer of 2000.
He's coming back to celebrate the millennium, right?
Not as a group.
Seo Tai Ji continues as a soloist.
What's wrong?
Are you disappointed?
That's...
just like Seo Tai Ji.
You need new music for the new millennium.
I kept my word. Can we go eat now?
- Sure. - Okay. Let's go.
- Seriously... - Go.
- Hurry up. - Nice.
This is the last time, okay?
One more time.
Order.
Okay.
You're here, Jin Do Jun.
Gosh.
It's really nice to see you in Prestigious Club.
It's so nice to see you.
We made a bet.
Seong Jun said...
you were a boring bookworm,
so you would never join our club.
Prestigious Club?
She's Seo Min Yeong, also a freshman...
of the Department of Law.
Hold on.
You're obedient.
You only did this.
She's a guest difficult to invite.
Seo Min Yeong from Hanil Girls' High School.
Her father is working in Seoul District Public Prosecutors' Office.
In the end, you're here.
As Do Jun's partner.
Anyway, welcome.
This is Ha In Seok. Jin Do Jun,
I mean, this is the route of 4-2.
You should have told me the truth from the beginning.
If I had known, I wouldn't have come.
Why did you bring me here?
- Because you're qualified. - What?
Seo Min Yeong, the only child of Seo Yoon Ho,
the deputy prosecutor...
of Seoul District Public Prosecutors' Office Special Unit.
It's a social gathering that suits you.
This Prestigious Club.
It's a social gathering?
Friendship where you back each other up when you're in trouble...
once you each hold a position after graduating?
Close-knit friendship...
that ignores law and policies as if they're nothing?
A social gathering, you said?
Not a gathering of potential criminals?
Don't be mistaken, Jin Do Jun.
What you can share here isn't deep friendship.
It's a strong privilege.
It doesn't suit me.
I never had such a privilege...
nor did I expect one.
You're the one who's mistaken, Seo Min Yeong.
So you think you're free from those privileges?
Because you entered the best university in Korea...
with the exam scores you worked hard to achieve with your smart brain.
The fact that you were able to focus solely on studying...
throughout the three years of high school.
And the fact that you can only focus...
on studying instead of worrying about making a living now.
Haven't you thought...
that it's thanks to your parents' financial and mental support?
The family of bench and bar for generations.
A healthy body and a smart brain.
Have you never thought...
that all of those were privileges given to you for free...
ever since you were born?
About Do Jun, sir.
He's adjusting well to his university life...
just like his peers.
- Is that so? - Now's the best time in life.
Even though he has 24 million dollars,
he's still young.
I wonder what he's thinking.
Oh, well.
You don't even know what your own son is thinking.
He is...
too distant of a family for me to know about him.
Hando Steel reported bankruptcy as they could not manage the debt...
from debt financing.
Hando Steel has a debt over four billion dollars in total.
Big social and economical impacts are expected.
The company that placed 1th in wealth ranking.
The company with the biggest debt of 4.2 billion dollars...
collapsed in vain.
Vice-Chairman Jin will attend the meeting...
with the creditors himself.
(Vice-Chairman's Office)
We have a problem, sir.
With the acquisition fund of 300 million dollars we prepared,
we might not be able to negotiate.
What are you saying now?
There's a company that offered 500 million dollars...
that the creditors demanded as the acquisition fund.
Is it Daeyoung?
Actually...
It's a foreign investment company.
Is there a special reason why a foreign company...
took over a big Korean company?
Are you going to take over Hando Steel?
Did you really offer 500 million dollars?
- Are you going to take over? - Please tell us!
- Why did you do it? - Did you take over the company...
at 500 million dollars?
Of course.
Power Shares is an investment company...
that focuses on the future value.
The 500 million dollars we offered is the future value of Hando Steel.
An American investment company, Power Shares.
Oh Se Hyeon, the representative of East Asia region.
(Detailed Profile)
He's an investment manager...
who invests in companies' future values.
He's a Korean-American who performs exceptionally well...
when it comes to company takeovers.
Future values?
Why would a foreign investment company...
that performed exceptionally well...
want to take over...
a weak and small company like Hando Steel?
Just why?
It's a chess piece.
There must be the chess board's owner.
The owner?
Whoever...
can't stand to watch Soonyang take over Hando Steel.
That person is...
the owner of the chess board.
(Three Way Restaurant)
- Gosh! - My goodness.
Gosh, Gyeong Hui. You said your back isn't well.
Oh, dear.
- You'll hurt your back. - It's okay.
- Goodness. - I can't believe this.
Gosh.
- Be careful. - Okay.
Goodness!
You'll hurt yourself.
Did you say he was Oh Se Hyeon?
Yes.
Dig into him.
What he's thinking...
and who he's meeting.
Yes, sir.
I shouldn't have gotten involved in the first place.
Because of you, I am breaking my first rule...
of investment for the first time.
The corporate value of Hando Steel is 500 million dollars?
No.
Nevertheless, the investor wants to invest in it? Yes.
Yes.
Tell me the reason, at least.
Why are you investing so recklessly?
Keep investors' secrets no matter what happens.
That's your investment rule, right?
I have to stop Hando Steel...
from falling into Vice-Chairman Jin's hands.
Vice-Chairman Jin?
He's your uncle. The successor of Soonyang.
You should be nice to your family, so why...
What you want...
isn't just Hando Steel?
In the end, what you want...
is Soonyang?
You want to become the owner of Soonyang?
(Soonyang Group)
(Reborn Rich)
Are you asking because you don't know,
or do you want to pretend that you don't know?
It's my present.
Do Jun.
I prepared it to welcome you.
Darn it.
Don't give me another presumptuous advice.
You're going to take over Hando Steel?
You want to beat Daeyoung so bad.
If you ever let Daeyoung take Hando Steel...
The person who gave Daeyoung the money is someone from Soonyang.
The eldest son succeeding. This isn't Joseon Dynasty.
I'll show Father who I am.
It's not over until it's over.
I never forgave those...
who went against me.